Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 314. Nestlé Milk Products (McCann & non-McCann Productions). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 21)
    - Nido: Basketball (Mexico) (Box 21)
    - Carnation Evaporada: Es Calidad (Mexico) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Kitchen Offer (Panama) (Box 21)
    - Leche Ideal: Child Singer (Panama) (Box 21)
    - Leche Ideal: Treehouse (Panama) (Box 21)
    - Carnation: Flowers (Philippines) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Strawberry Ice Cream (Peru) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Vanilla Ice Cream (Peru) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Chocolate Ice Cream (Peru) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Popsicles (Peru) (Box 21)
    - Leche Condensada: Cows (Spain) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: Child's Game (Taiwan) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: Cow Field (Taiwan) (Box 21)
    - Everyday: Many Countries (Taiwan) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: Child's Game (Thailand) (Box 21)
    - Nestlé UHT: Cow Field (Thailand) (Box 21)
    - Carnation: Row Boat (Thailand) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Picnic (Argentina) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Moms (Argentina) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Daydreaming Mom (Chile) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Baby Doll (Chile) (Box 21)
    - Brite: Everything White (Japan) (Box 21)
    - Krematop: Piano Romance (Japan) (Box 21)
    - Everyday: Stream (Malaysia) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: By Plane (Malaysia) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Growing Up (Middle East) (Box 21)
    - Nido: Number 1 Child (Philippines) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: Piano/Ballet (Singapore) (Box 21)
    - Nespray: Waking Up (Sri Lanka) (Box 21)
    - Collective campaign for condensed milk (Spain) (Box 21)
  - 315. Nestlé's/Quik: Rock Bunny, Baseballe Bunny. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:00
    - Quik: Rock Bunny (Box 21)
    - Quik: Baseball Bunny/CC (Box 21)
  - 316. Nescafé's Project: Re-cut Train, Narrative. 1984. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 21)
  - 317. 1979 Vevey Coffee Presentation (Part 1). 1979. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 21)
  - 318. 1979 Vevey Coffee Presentation (Part 2). 1979. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 21)
  - 319. 1979 Vevey Coffee Presentation (Part 3). 1979. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Tramp/Steamer (Box 21)
    - People Who Like People (Box 21)
    - Communication/CB/The Duke (Box 21)
    - Conversation/Art Gallery (Box 21)
    - Shares the Moment/Dolce Vita party (Box 21)
    - Soap Opera/Star Interview (Box 21)
    - Easy Rider (Box 21)
    - The Search/Missing (Box 21)
  - 320. 1979 Vevey Coffee Presentation (Part 4). 1979. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 21)
  - 321. Del Monte (Pineapple, Pears, Fruit in Juice, Orange Juice). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Del Monte: Pineapple (Box 21)
    - Del Monte: Pears (Box 21)
    - Del Monte: Fruit 'n Juice (Box 21)
    - Del Monte: Orange Juice (Box 21)
  - 322. Dr. Pepper Showreel (12 spots from Y&R). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Dr. Pepper regular/Pep Talk (Box 21)
    - Dr. Pepper regular/Swing (Box 21)
    - Bride and Groom (Box 21)
    - Dr. Pepper regular/Executive Lunch (Box 21)
    - Rain Dance (Box 21)
    - Luncheonette (Box 21)
    - Bellringer (Box 21)
    - Dr. Pepper sugar-free/Detective (Box 21)
    - Godzilla (Box 21)
    - Space Cowboy (Box 21)
    - Dr. Pepper sugar-free/Queen of Hearts (Box 21)
    - Cola Wars (Box 21)
  - 323. Ice Tea Productions--Summer 1986 Digital Production. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - STP (Box 21)
    - Rockwell International: Manage (Box 21)
    - Unisom (Box 21)
    - Sears (Box 21)
    - Vivitar (Box 21)
    - Rockwell International: Balance (Box 21)
    - Count Chocula Cereal (Box 21)
    - HBO: Behind The Scenes (Box 21)
    - Cinemax: Nostalgia (Box 21)
    - RC Cola (Box 21)
    - Golden Grahams (Box 21)
    - Rockwell International: Entrepreneur (Box 21)
    - Sony Super Walkman (Box 21)
    - WTBS (Box 21)
    - ABC (Box 21)
    - Samsung (Box 21)
    - Chanel No. 9 (Box 21)
    - Marvel Productions (Box 21)
    - Labyrinth (Box 21)
  - 324. Pepsi (Lionel Richie, Archeological Dig, Fighting Robots, Close Encounters, Sound Truck). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Pepsi: Lionel Richie (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Archaeological Dig (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Fighting Robots (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Close Encounters (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Sound Truck on Beach (Box 21)
  - 325. Rick Levine, Pepsi Campaign 1980.. 1980. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Pepsi: Catch That Pepsi Spirit montage (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Parade/Baton (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Lacrosse (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Skywriting (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Baseball Homecoming (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Rodeo (Box 21)
    - Pepsi: Welcome to the USA, Papa (Box 21)
  - 326. SF Milk (Run, Driving Lesson, Fridge, Party). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Milk: Run (Box 21)
    - Milk: Driving Lesson (Box 21)
    - Milk: Refrigerator (Box 21)
    - Milk: Party (Box 21)
  - 327. TAB--Girl on Beach. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Tab: Girl on Beach (Box 21)
  - 328. Swiss Miss, Quik, Milk. 1985-1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Swiss Miss Sugar Free: Judd Hirsch (Box 21)
    - Quik Sugar Free: Chocolate Milk Close-Up (Box 21)
    - Milk: Health Kick (Box 21)
  - 311. Nescafé Excella '85 Paris. Undated. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.Needs preservation rewind (Box 22)
  - 329. A Look At Cable Commercials. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 18:00
    - Intro by Judy Perkins (Box 22)
    - Kawasaki: Freedom (Box 22)
    - Chevy Camaro Z28: Shadows (Box 22)
    - Saran Wrap: Microwave Menu (Box 22)
    - Alpo: Lorne Greene (Box 22)
  - 330. Brazilian Reel Cable TV. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 10:00
    - Limago: Washing Liquid (Box 22)
    - Supermists: Colds (Box 22)
    - Chevrolet (Box 22)
    - Cornetto: Ice cream (Box 22)
    - Coca-Cola: Sports Hero (Box 22)
    - Chevrolet: Airplane (Box 22)
    - Shell Luma Oil: Gents Bathroom (Box 22)
    - Shell Responde (Box 22)
    - Topper: Football (Box 22)
    - Telephone: Volkswagen (Box 22)
    - Tergal: Telephone (Box 22)
    - Telephone: Street Death/Community Service (Box 22)
  - 331. McCann-Erickson Presents the Cable Network. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 22)
    [See also Tapes 332, 333, 334]
  - 332. McCann-Erickson Presents the Cable Network. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 22)
    [See also Tapes 331, 333, 334]
  - 333. Cable Networks. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 22)
    [See also Tapes 331, 332, 334. Similar to Tapes 331, 332 but without McCann agency narrator.]
  - 334. McCann-Erickson Presents the Cable Network. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 22)
    [See also Tapes 331, 332, 333]
  - 335. Cable TV Directors. Undated. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 22)
  - 336. Cable TV Spots. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Council For Cable Information (CCI): Personal Choice (Box 22)
    - Council For Cable Information (CCI): Best of Times (Box 22)
    - Council For Cable Information (CCI): A Few Good Moments (Box 22)
    - Council For Cable Information (CCI): Personal Choice (Box 22)
    - Council For Cable Information (CCI): Best of Times (Box 22)
  - 337. Video Journal #4. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Ad-supported cable television: a status report. Commercial resource: sample of cable commercials. Discussion over what cable is; how advertisers can use it; how viewership can be measured; differences from traditional networks; JWT's efforts at analyzing cable options; ad revenues; Infomercials--longer information-oriented commercials; client-sponsored programs.]
    - Chevy Camaro Z28: Shadows (Box 22)
    - No Nonsense/History of Women (Box 22)
    - Atari Pole Position: The Jerk (Box 22)
    - Berlei: Silkiss by Berlei (Box 22)
    - Corning: Nest Eggs (Box 22)
  - 338. Cable TV Commercials. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Pepto Bismol: Upset of the Week (Box 22)
    - Kal Kan: Lifetime Minute (Box 22)
    - Various WTBS commercials (Box 22)
    - Michelin: Winter Storm Update (Box 22)
    - Kraft: Rapper (Box 22)
    - Crisco: Country Artist Profiles (Box 22)
    - General Foods: Shortcuts (Box 22)
    - General Foods: Shortcuts (Box 22)
    - Doritos: Painted Wall (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Campbell's Chunky Soup: Soul Man (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Levi's: Blues (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Merry Go Round: Beach (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Honda Scooters: Walk on the Wild Side (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Pepsi: Child/Michael Jackson (MTV) (Box 22)
    - Swift: Sizzlean infomercial (Box 22)
    - Budweiser: After Work Bar (Box 22)
    - Quaker/Ken-L Ration: Lost Dog (Box 22)
    - Kawasaki: Freedom (Box 22)
    - United Technologies: Helicopter Businessman (Box 22)
  - 339. RJ Reynolds, Camel Filters. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Camel Filters: Drop Zone (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Drop Zone (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Drop Zone (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Dawn Departure (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Dawn Departure (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Dawn Departure (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Tent Raft (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Tent Raft (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Tent Raft (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: White Water Upstream (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: White Water Upstream (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: White Water Upstream (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Tire Change (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: Jeep Lean-To (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: River Wash (Box 22)
    - Camel Filters: The Letter (Box 22)
  - 340. Camel, Italian Spots: Idols, Seaplane, Boat. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Idols (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Seaplane (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Boat (Box 23)
  - 341. Camels Filter Int 1987 Film Release. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 6:00
    - Camel Filters: Portage (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Short Cut (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Jeep Storm (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Base Trek (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Portage (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Short Cut (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Jeep Storm (Box 23)
    - Camel Filters: Base Trek (Box 23)
  - 342. Silk Cut Cigarettes. 1986. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 23)
  - 343. Bon Jour: Lenita, Jodi, Alexa. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Bon Jour clothing: Laura (Lenita) (Box 23)
    - Bon Jour clothing: Bill Bailey Dance (Jodi) (Box 23)
    - Bon Jour clothing: Alexa (Box 23)
    - Bon Jour clothing: Laura (Lenita) with Bloomingdale's tagline (Box 23)
    - Bon Jour clothing: bill Bailey Dance (Jodi) with Bloomingdale's tagline (Box 23)
    - Bon Jour clothing: Alexa with Bloomingdale's tagline (Box 23)
  - 344. Calvin Revised. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:26
    - Calvin Klein Fragrance, underwear, Obsession montage (Box 23)
  - 345. Calvin Klein. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:30
    - Calvin Klein: Brooke Shields (Box 23)
    - Calvin Klein: Brooke Shields (Box 23)
    - Calvin Klein: Brooke Shields (Box 23)
  - 346. Morty Everds NYC Trends in Fashion and Beauty. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 23)
    [See also Tape 361. Interview-type magazine show looking at the new populism of the Imperfect Perfect Beauty; character over plastic beauty. Interviews with Andy Warhol, Helen Gurley-Brown, Iman, etc.]
  - 347. Guess Jeans, New York. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Guess Jeans: Desert/Horse Branding (Box 23)
  - 348. Lee. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:30
    - Lee Jeans: Lee Maniac Girl (Box 23)
    - Lee Jeans: Lee Maniac Couple (Box 23)
    - Lee Jeans: Lee Maniac Guy (Box 23)
  - 349. Levi Strauss, Gym. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00
    - Levi's: Gym (Box 23)
  - 350. Levi's Jeans, Do You Fit the Legend. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 00:30
    - Levi's: Do You Fit the Legend? (Box 23)
  - 351. Levi's, Not Just By Jeans Alone. 1981. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [A video report on the saturated but changing jeans market. A look at what they are doing now--creating new products and markets rather than only filling the need for jeans. The Levi's Tailored Classic line of slacks, sportcoats, and 3-piece suits. A peek at the consumer research behind the launch of this clothing line.]
    - Levi's: Not Just By Jeans Alone (Box 23)
  - 352. Levi's 501 Blues Campaign. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Levi 501 Blues: Gang (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Motion Study (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Blues Singer (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Girls (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Rooftop Dance (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Watcher (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Street Singers (Box 23)
    - Levi 501 Blues: Jive montage (Box 23)
  - 353. Anne Klein Parfum Rev. 2; Anne Klein Parfum; Kornhauser and Calene Parlux. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Anne Klein Parfum: Anne Klein Woman rev. 1 (Box 23)
  - 354. Kornhauser & Calene; Parlux; Anne Klein Parfum: Anne Klein Woman Rev 2. 1984. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 23)
  - [355: Missing] (Box 23)
  - 356. Drakkar Noir Quick Cuts Umatic. TRT: 00:30 (Box 24)
  - 357. McCann-Erickson France. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - L'Oreal Preference: You Can (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal Preference: Smart Blonde ver. 2 (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal Preference: Smart Blonde (Box 24)
  - 358. L'Oreal. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - L'Oreal/Crème Riche Lipstick: Llips in Mirror (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Crème Riche Lipstick: Close-Up Fingernails (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Shadow Riche Eye Shadows: Close-Up Eye Shadow (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/French Formula Riche Mascara: Close-Up Eyes (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Visuelle Makeup Fluide: Close-Up Faces (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Visuelle Makeup Fluide: Close-Up Faces (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Freehold Styling Mousse: Feeling Free (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Freehold Styling Mousse: Feeling Free (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Performing Preference: White Linen (Box 24)
    - L'Oreal/Performing Preference: White Linen (Box 24)
  - 359. L'Oreal Coloracion. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 24)
  - 360. MCE/L'Oreal Studio Line Video. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - L'Oreal/Studio Line beauty products: Video Studio (Box 24)
  - 361. Marty Everds: NYC Beauty/Fashion Tape (For L'Oreal). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 24)
    [See also Tape 346]
  - [362: Missing] (Box 24)
  - 363. 1 Spot: Revlon-Charlie. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Revlon/Charlie: You're Very Charlie (Box 24)
  - 364. Grey Advertising: Revlon Charlie. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 00:30 (Box 24)
  - 365. Charlie. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Revlon/Charlie: Dancing (Box 24)
  - 366. And You Call That Creative?. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 37:00
    - National Light Bulbs: Fruit (Japan) (Box 24)
    - Polaroid: Party (US) (Box 24)
    - Sony Hi-Fi: Role Reversal (UK) (Box 24)
    - Vision Saucepans: Melting Test (Australia) (Box 24)
    - Knirps Umbrella: Car Wash (UK) (Box 24)
    - Energen Cracottes: Dog (UK) (Box 24)
    - Dulux: Snooker (UK) (Box 24)
    - Pontin's: Esther Williams (UK) (Box 24)
    - Ali Coffee: Gone with the Wind (Norway) (Box 24)
    - Airport Shops: Lovers' Tiff (France) (Box 24)
    - John Smith's Yorkshire Bitter: Performing Dog (UK) (Box 24)
    - Unipart Auto Parts: Rolling Caption (UK) (Box 24)
    - Newcastle Brown Ale: Astronaut (UK) (Box 24)
    - Cointreau: Original (UK) (Box 24)
    - Cointreau: Reunion (UK) (Box 24)
    - Maxell: The Usual (US) (Box 24)
    - Heineken: Boomerang (UK) (Box 24)
    - Fiat: Interview (Brazil) (Box 24)
    - Johnson and Johnson: Mother and Child (Brazil) (Box 24)
    - Visa: Presenter (Spain) (Box 24)
    - John Courage Beer: Animatic (UK) (Box 24)
    - John Courage Beer: Final Film (UK) (Box 24)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Rubik's Cube (UK) (Box 24)
    - Heineken: Video Game (UK) (Box 24)
    - Benson & Hedges montage (Box 24)
    - Benson & Hedges imitators montage (Box 24)
    - Heinz Tomato Sauce (Box 24)
    - Sound of Products montage (Box 24)
    - Pop Promo montage (Box 24)
    - Wallpaper (UK) (Box 24)
    - YSL (France) (Box 24)
    - New Graphics montage (Box 24)
    - Close-Up Lens montage (Box 24)
    - Computer animation montage (Box 24)
    - Brand property montage (Box 24)
    - Summary montage (Box 24)
  - 367. GM/ISUZU: The Asian Region Creative Trends; Presented by Barrington Hill, Creative Director, McCann Tokyo. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 17:45 (Box 24)
    [Creative trends in general, in automotive advertising; GM advertising profile; Status is a key selling point in the Asian region outside of Japan; Westernization is also a high selling point. In Japan, they don't want anything logical, but there are no other rules. Creating a human personality, visual effect is very important.]
  - 368. Australia Creative Reel. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 14:00
    - Sunday Telegraph: Table for One (Box 24)
    - Bubble Yum: Pop Music (Box 24)
    - Reach Toothbrush: Cartoon (Box 24)
    - Sunday Telegraph: Young, Rich, and Addicted (Box 24)
    - Nestlé: Jenny/Homework (Box 24)
    - Coke: 9 to 5 (Box 24)
    - Goodyear Vector: Tires with Grip (Box 24)
    - Nescafé Blend 43: It's a Pleasure (Box 24)
    - Homestead Motor Inn: Friendly (Box 24)
    - Caltex Techron Concentrate: Extra Passengers (Box 24)
    - Diet Coke: Sports (Box 24)
    - Diet Coke: Sport/Travel (Box 24)
    - Black & Decker Marathon Hammer Drill: Home Addition (Box 24)
    - Pampas Pastry: Tea-Time Treats (Box 24)
    - Pampas Pastry: Mincemeat (Box 24)
    - Pampas Pastry: Canned Fruit (Box 24)
    - BHP: W. Hunter (Box 24)
    - Planter's Honey Roast: Billboard (Box 24)
    - Holden Astra (GMH): Clever (Box 24)
    - Holden Astra (GMH): Clever (Box 24)
    - AMCOR: Investment/Expansion (Box 24)
    - Radio Station 5AD: The Cardwell-Harvey Report (Box 24)
    - Queensland Electricity Stock: Winds of Fortune (Box 24)
  - 369. Canada Creative Reel. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Sprite: To the Top (Box 24)
    - Del Monte: Dis-A-Spearing (Box 24)
    - Gelco: Night Moves (Box 24)
    - Calais: Billboard (Box 24)
    - Tetley: Time and Motion (Box 24)
    - Ikea: Systems (Box 24)
    - Labatt's: Piano Player (Box 24)
    - Labatt's: Beach (Box 24)
    - B.C. Dairy: Clock (Box 24)
    - B.C. Dairy: Studio (Box 24)
    - Coke: Launch/Walk (Box 24)
    - Minute Maid: Whoosh (Box 24)
    - Ikea: Newlyweds (Box 24)
    - Better Cheddars: Better, Better, Better (Box 24)
  - 370. McCann-Erickson Worldwide Creative Reel (Edited for Detroit). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tapes 381, 382]
    - Nescafé: Cities of the World/Art School (Japan) (Box 24)
    - Nescafé Decaf: Natural (USA) (Box 24)
    - GM Pickup: Train Tracks (Mexico) (Box 24)
    - Opel Corsa: Car as Horse (Spain) (Box 24)
    - Esso: Tiger (France) (Box 24)
    - Kodak: First Step (UK) (Box 24)
    - Camels: Adventure/Statues (Italy) (Box 24)
    - Black & Decker: Dustbuster (France) (Box 24)
    - Martini Bianco: Pop (UK) (Box 24)
    - Swatch: French Fashion (Switzerland) (Box 24)
    - Levi's: Living Legend (Canada) (Box 24)
    - Coca-Cola: 9 to 5 (Australia) (Box 24)
    - Coca-Cola: Sizzle (International team) (Box 24)
    - Tiger Beer: Close-Up Pour (Singapore) (Box 24)
    - Castlemaine Fourex Beer: Workers (Melbourne) (Box 24)
    - Loburg Beer: Shadows (Belgium) (Box 24)
    - Alka Seltzer: Three Alarm Chili (USA) (Box 24)
    - Sony: King Kong (USA) (Box 24)
    - Imec: Bride (Italy) (Box 24)
    - Milk: Pole Vaulter (USA) (Box 24)
    - Eiser Pantyhose: Romance/Intrigue (Finland) (Box 24)
    - Finn Crystal: Glasses (Finland) (Box 24)
    - Community Chest: Signing Mime (Singapore) (Box 24)
    - MOT Seat Belts: Buckle Your Baby (New Zealand) (Box 24)
    - Stand Up for Singapore: 25 Years of Nation Building (Singapore) (Box 24)
    - Client montage (Box 24)
  - 371. Creative Review, McCann Madrid: Future Creativity is Calling: It's for youuuuuuuuuuuu!. 1986. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown.
    - Seat Ibiza (Box 24)
    - Talbot Solara (Box 24)
    - Opel Corsa (Box 24)
    - Kadett (Box 24)
    - Kodak promotions (Box 24)
    - Kodak promotions (Box 24)
    - Asturias (Box 24)
    - Canary Islands (Box 24)
    - Vita (Box 24)
    - Tulipan (Box 24)
    - Flora (Box 24)
    - Ligeresa (Box 24)
    - Pepsi-Cola: Arqueology (Box 24)
    - Coca-Cola: Train (Box 24)
    - Citroën CX (Box 24)
    - Opel Corsa (Box 24)
    - Kas (Box 24)
    - Sprite (Box 24)
    - Pirelli (Box 24)
    - Danone (Box 24)
    - La Moda (Box 24)
    - Lois Shoes (Box 24)
    - Freixenet (Box 24)
    - Alpine (Box 24)
    - Cloe (Box 24)
    - Compari (Box 24)
    - Spa (Box 24)
    - Nivea (Box 24)
  - 372. McCann-Erickson Singapore Creative Showreel, Creative Awards 1987. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 25)
    - Standard Chartered: A Better Spot (Box 25)
    - Habitat/Mothercare: Chairs (Box 25)
    - Martell Cognac: White Gloves (Box 25)
    - Community Chest: Blind Child Narrator (Box 25)
    - Ribbon Dancer (Box 25)
    - Air Force: Fighter Planes (Box 25)
    - Print advertisement montage (Box 25)
    - Commercial montage (Box 25)
  - 373. The Creative Strategy: Clive Rumsey/Stu Eaton. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Barry Day commentary and introduction; importance/necessity of defining the creative strategy for a product/client; Clive Rumsey and Stu Eaton delve into the reason, definition, purpose, criterion, and objectives of the creative strategy; strategy is a single idea linking a consumer need to the product benefit in such a way as to produce the most persuasive consumer response.]
    - Martini Bianco: World in a Bottle (Box 25)
    - Coke montage (Box 25)
    - Esso montage (Box 25)
    - Kodak montage (Box 25)
    - Martini montage (Box 25)
  - 374. Print Montage and Worldwide Showreel from Creatively Speaking. 1988. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 20:00
    - American Express: Jacuzzi (USA) (Box 25)
    - L'Oreal: Fashion Parade (France) (Box 25)
    - Isuzu: Tango (Japan) (Box 25)
    - French's: 9 1/2 Weeks (Venezuela) (Box 25)
    - Unilever: Bresigny (Belgium) (Box 25)
    - Stefanal Kids: Leisurewear (Italy) (Box 25)
    - Shearson: Horses (USA) (Box 25)
    - Sprite: Best of Sports (Argentina) (Box 25)
    - William Lawson: Billiards (UK) (Box 25)
    - Smirnoff: Good Friends (Jamaica) (Box 25)
    - Coca-Cola: Kitchen (Argentina) (Box 25)
    - Coca-Cola: Day in the Life (Japan) (Box 25)
    - Ikea: Day of the Opening (Canada) (Box 25)
    - California Milk: The Run (USA) (Box 25)
    - Evening Post: Paperboy (UK) (Box 25)
    - Atlanta Journal: Night Time (USA) (Box 25)
    - Advertising Council: Rush (USA) (Box 25)
    - P&O: Cruise (UK) (Box 25)
    - Coppertone: New Sun (Japan) (Box 25)
    - Waterworld: The Edge (USA) (Box 25)
    - Chesebrough: Sensitive Skin (USA) (Box 25)
    - Winchell's: Car Pool (USA) (Box 25)
    - Delight: Grass is Greener (UK) (Box 25)
    - Nestlé Quik: Singing in the Rain (USA) (Box 25)
    - National Dairy: Late Bloomer (USA) (Box 25)
    - Martini Bianco: Sky Screen (UK) (Box 25)
    - The Informer (Ireland) (Box 25)
  - 375. MBA Creative Contract. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Barry Day on creative strategy. McCann way to create a creative strategy: find the truths about the product first; use them; guidelines of what a strategy must have without having too much; going over the creative contract--a form for creating and guiding the strategy (4 parts)--action to be created, prospect profile, creative strategy, net takeaway--each part explained.]
    - Buick: John Houseman/Financing (Box 25)
    - AT&T Business Long Distance: Milton (Box 25)
    - Del Monte Pineapple Spears: Dis-A-Spearing (Box 25)
  - 376. MBA Creative Contract--Master. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Same as Tape 375. Must listen to on Ch-2 option, otherwise loud hiss distorts audio.]
    - Buick: John Houseman/Financing (Box 25)
    - AT&T Business Long Distance: Milton (Box 25)
    - Del Monte Pineapple Spears: Dis-A-Spearing (Box 25)
  - 377. North America Region--Creative Reel. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tapes 383, 384]